{
"question": "体",
"answer": "からだ"
},
{
"question": "大きい",
"answer": "おおきい"
},
{
"question": "質問",
"answer": "しつもん"
},
{
"question": "夕べ",
"answer": "ゆうべ"
},
{
"question": "有名",
"answer": "ゆうめい"
},
{
"question": "兄",
"answer": "あに"
},
{
"question": "歌う",
"answer": "うたう"
},
{
"question": "上る",
"answer": "のぼる"
},
{
"question": "鳥",
"answer": "とり"
},
{
"question": "服",
"answer": "ふく"
},
{
"question": "時々",
"answer": "ときどき"
},
{
"question": "妹",
"answer": "いもうと"
},
{
"question": "二つ",
"answer": "ふたつ"
},
{
"question": "頼む",
"answer": "たのむ"
},
{
"question": "今朝",
"answer": "けさ"
},
{
"question": "お父さん",
"answer": "おとうさん"
},
{
"question": "遅い",
"answer": "おそい"
},
{
"question": "借りる",
"answer": "かりる"
},
{
"question": "薬",
"answer": "くすり"
},
{
"question": "庭",
"answer": "にわ"
},
